Guys welcome you all again to a new
video.  This is the Hero Splendor bike I have
and this is my own bike.  But here
I am sharing with you all with great sadness that
look, there was an accident with the bike.  The bike crashed.
But nothing happened to the boy who was driving this bike
because he was wearing a helmet and bike
shoes, that is, he was driving the bike wearing shoes.
He did not feel even a slight pain.
But the bike's brother is in such
bad condition that it seems nothing has changed.  Now you
guys please comment and tell me in which hour the bike
accident happened because the
number plate of the bike is bent here from the front.
Its visor is damaged.  And also it should be mentioned
that the indicator is damaged from here.
Also, the mirror of the bike has got damaged here.
Lagarde crashed it.   The
bike has been worn for a very long time.
And you can see the condition of the trunk here.
Its trunk is properly bent.
Its trunk is broken.
Look where its framing has gone.  And
talk to the rear.  The rear element is out and the
bike is mounted on a centre stand.
And you can take a look from the rear here.
Look where the motor guard is and
where the bike wheel is.  There is so much alignment
and the only reason for the alignment coming out is
that the rear
chassis of the bike has slipped and
gone to the right side.  Although the accident happened on the
left side, the chassis
went to the right side and its wheel
went to the left side.  And also
look at both the rear shock absorbers here,
these shockers have become quite bent.  The shocker is
broken from here.  It was pressed here.  Now
I also don't understand what it was about brother.
Look, the stand sensor has been fixed.  The
stand is tied because there is
probably a stand sensor installed here.  Its
spring has come out.  The stand will remain down at any time.
Like if you start the bike and put it in gear, it
stops.  That's why the
stand is tied here.  I am looking at you very
badly brother, what should I tell
you.  Now, let's say the bike
is insured now.  Then we will make an insurance claim.
One year back is not over yet.   It has been only
10 months since the back.
10 or something from the back is 11 months old.  If we make a claim then
our process will be completed.
And the bag will be made in insurance right now.
So let's quickly
complete the process by making an insurance claim right now.
And just now we came to Shiv Shakti
Hero showroom near Madhubani Shiv Shakti Hero showroom,
but it is a little far from the showroom because
its service centre is separate and the showroom is separate
and here you can see that there are many new bikes
parked there.  So brother, we just
visited here.  Now let's get its processing
completed and
claim the bike in the insurance and only
after talking to sir we will know
in how many days the bike will be delivered to us or will he
give it to us immediately because there is a lot of damage in the bike.
Guys, look here
we have deposited the car
in insurance for accidental service.  Look, it is
written here 'Accidental Service'.  The vehicle has been deposited
and all the necessary documents are attached with it.
To claim insurance, your bike must have
first part insurance.   There
should not be an insurance file.  There
should be proper insurance.  That too first
part company recruitment.  Along with that, you have to
bring the original insurance of the vehicle.
Original vehicle owner book, original
driving license, original PAN card and
original Aadhar card.  All these documents are
with you.  Whenever you make an insurance claim,
your insurance should not be on file.
And I still had proper
insurance, so we have deposited the car.
We got the vehicle entered and
all this was given to us through this token number also.  The bike will have to be
left at the service centre for a few days
because brother, the bike has met with a very bad
accident, which you can tell from the back, brother,
look at
its motor guard which is fitted here, brother,
this is the main problem, see brother,
your insurance is the first part but how
old is it, I have also taken that for now, the
insurance of the bike was 9 to 10
months old as I told you, so it is a brand
new bike here,
so now let us see how much percentage the
insurance covers, the value of the insurance is
written here brother, the total
value is
₹76,866, right now the value of the bike is the insurance.
Now let us see
how much the company covers for damage.  Suppose it is 2 years then the
percentage will be deducted at that time also.   The
bike has been insured for 3 years.   Even if there is
first part insurance at that time,
percentage will be deducted.  So this is how the
percentage is deducted.  It is not that it will provide full cover.
But how much percentage it will cost will be
known only after the bike is made.
See.  So guys, you should see
how the bike met with the accident in a very bad condition.
And this bike of
ours has just been made and completed.
I got a call from the service centre of Shiv Shakti Hero showroom
that sir your bike has been repaired.
Come and visit the service center.  So
we have just come to the service center.  So
my bike is finally ready.  The damage to this bike was the
front visor, mirror
damage and trunk damage.  Both shockers and
you were shown in the video.  The rear motor
guard was also damaged and the chassis of the bike
looked a bit bent.  But now regarding the chassis,
sir told me that the chassis is proper.   There was some
damage so I got it repaired.
Now I don't know what I did or not.
But he said that the insurance
team came and visited.  He said that your
chassis was
not as damaged as it should have been.  There was damage exactly equal to MM, so
he got it repaired.  Due to which I have
not received a single rupee budget.  And with that
our bike was ready.  The chassis of the bike
no longer seems to be banded at all.
We have taken the bike for a test drive.  Only
after that I shot the video
because it is my job to give good reviews to you
people and I am finding the bike
absolutely comfortable to ride.
Looks like brand new.  There doesn't seem to be any damage anywhere.
And also the
trunk of the first Stars was installed.  So right now I have got the
Steel World trunk in it which
I got from the company.  That means you
people keep saying that brother does
not give the trunk in insurance, then there is nothing like that
brother.  The
insurance company pays according to the parts installed inside the bike.  It's not like
I had to pay for the trunk separately.  Nothing was
given separately.  The back has never been
washed.  So we talked to sir and he said
brother, you can get the washing done.  But
you will have to pay the washing charge separately.  This is
not all there is to insurance.  If you want, you
can get it done outside or if you get it done in our service centre, you will have to
pay for washing separately.
Rest, in the same hour in which the back was to be made,
my back was made and completed properly.
In which there is a trunk, visor,
mirror, leg guard and rear murder
guard.  All the indicators were broken.  The trunk was
damaged.  The
insurance company has covered only the part that was damaged.
Also the chassis of the bike was properly repaired.   There was
no need to replace the chassis right now and my bike was
completed in just three days.  If the chase had been
damaged, it could have taken a very long time.
I am talking about the first part insurance.
It is not that look what is happening with bikes now, if
you buy a new bike for one year, then there is
one year first part
insurance and 4 years third party insurance.
As soon as third party insurance arrives, get it
renewed.  Contact the Near Service
Center not the after market vendor.  Get
your insurance completed from the nearest service centre
so that you do not face any problem in making a claim.
Something similar happened to me.  There was a back
in insurance.  There was an accident.  I did not face
any problem.  Nothing
happened.  There was no problem at all.  Because the
insurance service center was recommended.  I had a
driver's license in my own name and I had
also met with an accident.  Earlier I had
told you that my friend was
driving the bike.  But I was driving the bike myself.  This happened to
me myself, the
bike was damaged but
look at my hand I have got a little scratch but only that much my
hand got rubbed because
we were wearing helmets on our heads so the helmet got rubbed,
otherwise there was no damage to the bike, well
I did not suffer any damage to the bike, earlier I had
told you guys that my friend was driving the bike
but my friend was not driving,
I was driving the bike myself brother, now let me
show you from the rear,
in what position the motor guard is and if you are
new to the channel then brother subscribe, so
guys, now look at the bike from the rear,
both the wheels
are in the proper middle centre of the motor guard, our bike is
ready.  What did you feel at first?  The chassis
seemed to be rushed into this position.  But right now the
chassis of the back is in the proper center.   The
number plate is on its side from inside,
brother.  Because its number plate will
remain in the old motor guard.  So after
cutting it, it will be pinched again inside it.  The
trunk and the valve are all installed and if
you talk about the back and the front, you will see that the
visor assembly is new.  Motor guard means
that whatever part of it was damaged, all the
parts were covered by the insurance company.   The
soccer ball in the front is also correct.  If
you have any roof or chassis or if there was some bend in it, then get it
repaired with a lathe or from wherever it was done.  I don't know all of them.   Immediately
after the bike was made, I got a direct call saying
that sir, your bike is ready.  We
talked on call about the condition of the chassis?   He
said, have you got the chassis repaired or whatever
chassis you got done, I don't know what all was done or not in the proper 20 centre.
But both
saucers are my damage.  So brothers, look at both the enthusiasts,
brand new ones are given here.  You will get a great
buttery feel.  You will get a new feeling
brother.  And here you can see that
all the bikes will be claimed here in insurance only.
Here you see,
all the bikes are covered under insurance.  The mechanic brother is working on all the bikes from one side.  You have
made my bike brother, it is nicely made, isn't it?  Look, and
here is the insurance spare counter, brother, there is
no tension for the spare and right now we are on the ground floor,
bike service work is going on on the first floor, we will
show it to you in the service centre
and if your bike meets with an accident and you
go to the service centre and they say that
this will not happen, this will not happen, then
you can also talk to the insurance company on the
toll free number, but I did
not have to talk to anyone, brother,
because all the papers were correct, the driving
license was in my own name, so I did
not have to talk to anyone, the
back was made very easily, your papers are up to date, so there is
no tension in getting the bike insured.  I am suggesting only one thing to you people.
Whenever your bike
insurance is filed, get it done immediately.  First of all,
keep your insurance up to date.  Get
your insurance updated two days before filing.  This will ensure that the
insurance company knows that the bike
accident was not an accident.
Insurance guy keeps the proper up to date.
Due to which you will not face any problem in insurance claim.
Look, my bike has been
finalized and there is
not a single expense in the insurance journey.  Only the claim
charge that I have incurred is ₹350. Here is the gate pass
and this is the bill.  He will take it at the gate
as soon as he takes delivery of the bike, but we have
not taken the bike delivery yet.